<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on n0k0m3 Dev Blog</title>
    <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on n0k0m3 Dev Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://n0k0m3.github.io/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Arch - Part 5 - Bugs Fixes</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/bug_fixes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/bug_fixes/</guid>
      <description>OBS Studio flickering with Intel Graphics With some Intel graphics cards on XOrg (in my case, Tiger Lake Xe), OBS Studio will flicker with screen capture.
sudo nano /etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/20-intel.conf Section &amp;#34;Device&amp;#34; Identifier &amp;#34;Intel Graphics&amp;#34; Driver &amp;#34;modesetting&amp;#34; EndSection Reboot or restart XOrg server to apply the fix.
Delete Goodix Fingerprint Sensor saved fingerprint data If you installed Windows and enrolled fingerprints with Goodix Fingerprint Sensor, the saved fingerprint data will prevent new enrollments in Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide for hacking PSVita on Linux</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/ps_vita_hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/ps_vita_hacking/</guid>
      <description>Follow instructions from https://guide.13375384.xyz/start or https://vita.hacks.guide/.
Documents for compiling from sources for tools. Guide to mount TexFAT Note: Put device in airplane mode during the Content Manager connection process will make the steps much easier to do.
DON&amp;rsquo;T MANUALLY SETTING YAMT, JUST USE YAMT SETUP USING VITADEPLOY (guide)
FinalHE Check prerequisites (https://github.com/soarqin/finalhe)
git clone https://github.com/soarqin/finalhe cd finalhe qmake &amp;amp;&amp;amp; make Build artifacts in src/FinalHE. Copy VitaDeploy zip in the same folder as FinalHE binary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Arch - Part 4 - Tips and Tricks</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/tips_and_tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/tips_and_tricks/</guid>
      <description>fstab mount with user permssion Use KDE/GNOME partition manager to manage mount point and use mount options: uid=1000,gid=1001,umask=022
Or append to /etc/fstab:
UUID=&amp;lt;disk_UUID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;mount_point&amp;gt; &amp;lt;format&amp;gt; uid=1000,gid=1001,umask=022,noatime 0 1 fstab mount NTFS with kernel NTFS3 driver from kernel 5.15 Use KDE/GNOME partition manager to manage mount point, this will use the default mount.ntfs -&amp;gt; ntfs-3g driver. We need to change the mount driver to mount.ntfs3 in /etc/fstab:
UUID=&amp;lt;disk_UUID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;mount_point&amp;gt; ntfs3 discard,noatime 0 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Arch - Part 3 - Post-Installation Setup</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/post_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/post_install/</guid>
      <description>Install zsh4humans I don&amp;rsquo;t need anything more fancy than romkatv&amp;rsquo;s zsh4humans
sh -c &amp;#34;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/n0k0m3/Personal-Setup/main/Setting_up_Arch/setup.sh)&amp;#34; Install Nextcloud sudo pacman -S nextcloud-client Sync .dotfiles with Nextcloud + flameshot shortcut
Setting up pacman and makepkg config sudo nano /etc/pacman.conf Set ParallelDownloads = 10:
sudo nano /etc/makepkg.conf Set compile flags CFLAGS=&amp;quot;-march=native -mtune=native ...&amp;quot; and MAKEFLAGS=&amp;quot;-j12&amp;quot; for 12 being total number of available cores/threads:
Comparing current installation with installed packages of previous dist python3 read_install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Arch - Part 2 - `systemd` hooks with FIDO2 unlock</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/systemd_setup/systemd_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/systemd_setup/systemd_setup/</guid>
      <description>By default Arch-based distros uses busybox init, which doesn’t support some features comfort from systemd. This guide will help you to setup systemd hooks, switch encryption to LUKS2 for systemd-cryptenroll, use U2F/FIDO2 key to unlock at boot, and Plymouth for boot splash screen.
systemd hooks and Plymouth boot splash screen Follwing script will change busybox init to systemd hooks and setup plymouth with colorful_loop theme.
Requirements: yay (default on EndeavourOS)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Arch - Part 1 - Swap on BTRFS</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/setting_up_arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/setting_up_arch/setting_up_arch/</guid>
      <description>This is setup on EndeavourOS/Manjaro, on barebone Arch should be a little bit different (install yay before all of these steps)
Arch setup Setting up Manjaro/EndeavourOS with Calamares installer using this partition Setup with SWAP file (turn on hibernation option):
Partition Mount Point Filesystem Size Encryption Status EFI system partition /boot/efi FAT32 300-550 MB Unencrypted /boot partition /boot/efi ext4 200-500 MB Unencrypted root partition / btrfs/LUKS Rest of space Encrypted Note: mount EFI with boot flag and / with root flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tensorflow with GPU support in Docker</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/tensorflow_docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/tensorflow_docker/</guid>
      <description>Following guide was tested on EndeavourOS and Manjaro (Arch-based) Linux distro.
Why? Installing dependencies and setting up notebooks is usually a PITA: installing CUDA with CuDNN and TensorRT doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a common and easy to follow guide, along with recent (not recent) release of python 3.9, most ML/DL packages are not updated to this wheel. Also setting up venv is hard to maintain and migrate as you have to backup the whole environment to other machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFIO Single GPU Passthrough Guide on Linux</title>
      <link>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/single_gpu_passthrough_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://n0k0m3.github.io/posts/single_gpu_passthrough_guide/</guid>
      <description>Why single GPU passthrough? Because I&amp;rsquo;m poor, using Ryzen non-APU CPU, and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to buy a second GPU just for passthrough. I&amp;rsquo;m using a single GPU passthrough for gaming on Windows and using Linux as my daily driver.
In this guide, we will be going over how to set up a single GPU passthrough on Linux. This guide is meant to be a reference for myself and others who want to learn how to set up a single GPU passthrough on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
